Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
- Series II: Articles/Essays
  - Subseries A: Notes, Drafts and Research
    - "Injustice in Austria" open letter, NYR, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - "Could the French Have Won?" review of Strange Victory: Hitler's Conquest of France, NYR, draft, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Could the French Have Won?" review of Strange Victory: Hitler's Conquest of France, NYR, draft, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Could the French Have Won?" review of Strange Victory: Hitler's Conquest of France, NYR, notes, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "Could the French Have Won?" review of Strange Victory: Hitler's Conquest of France, NYR, notes, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Could the French Have Won?" review of Strange Victory: Hitler's Conquest of France, NYR, notes, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "Europe is One--Until Disaster Strikes," NYT, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Introduction to Camus's The Plague, 2001 edition, drafts, notes, correspondence, 1998, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Introduction to Camus's The Plague, 2001 edition, drafts, notes, correspondence, 1998, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "Alice im Euroland," Die Zeit, research, draft, notes, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Alice im Euroland," Die Zeit, research, draft, notes, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "The White House and the World," NYR, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "'Ciuma - o metaforă a timpului nostru," Orizont, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "Mésentente Cordiale," Newsweek En Français, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "'Twas a Famous Victory," NYR, drafts, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "'Twas a Famous Victory," NYR, drafts, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "'Twas a Famous Victory," NYR, drafts, notes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "'Twas a Famous Victory," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - "Rehearsal for Evil," review of Spain Betrayed: The Soviet Union in the Spanish Civil War, TNR, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "The French Difference," review of Les cartes de la Franche a l'heure del la mondialisation..., NYR, draft, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - "The French Difference," review of Les cartes de la Franche a l'heure del la mondialisation..., NYR, draft, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - "The French Difference," review of Les cartes de la Franche a l'heure del la mondialisation..., NYR, draft, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - "The French Difference," review of Les cartes de la Franche a l'heure del la mondialisation..., NYR, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - "The French Difference," review of Les cartes de la Franche a l'heure del la mondialisation..., NYR, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - "The French Difference: An Exchange," NYR, Frederic Bozo reaction, Judt response, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - "The End of History," review of Troublemaker: The Life and History of A.J.P. Taylor, TNR, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "The End of History," review of Troublemaker: The Life and History of A.J.P. Taylor, TNR, draft, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, drafts, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, draft, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, draft, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, press, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, sources, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, sources, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, sources, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, notes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, notes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses "offended", 2001 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses "offended - irony", 2001 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses "pro + intelligent dissent", 2001 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses "factual critical", 2001 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses "mad", 2001 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses, 2001-2001 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - "Romania: Bottom of the Heap," NYR, responses, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - "On 'The Plague,'" NYR, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - "Burst," TNR, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - "Schmerzhafte Lehre: Amerika muss umdenken," Deutsche Zeitung, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - "The War on Terror," NYR, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - "America and the War," NYR, drafts, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - "America and the War," NYR, drafts, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - "America and the War," NYR, drafts, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - "America and the War," NYR, drafts, notes, research, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - "America and the War," NYR responses, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - "America and the War," NYR, responses, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - "America, The War and Israel: An Exchange," NYR, research, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - "America and the War," NYR, responses, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - "America and the War," NYR, responses, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - "America, The War and Israel: An Exchange," NYR, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - "America, The War and Israel: An Exchange," NYR responses, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - "America, The War and Israel: An Exchange," NYR responses, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR, notes, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR, research, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR, research, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR, research, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR, draft, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - "The Road to Nowhere: An Exchange," NYR research, draft, correspondence, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - "The Road to Nowhere: An Exchange," NYR drafts, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - "The Road to Nowhere: An Exchange," NYR notes, research, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - "The Road to Nowhere: An Exchange," NYR notes, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - "The Road to Nowhere: An Exchange," NYR notes, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Favorable letters, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Favorable letters, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - NYU letters, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Agree but...letters (Algeria), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - More sorrow than anger letters, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Agree but...letters (Taba), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Very critical letters (focus on Taba, Arafat's rejection of Barak, [illegible] of YA), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Mad letters (A-sem. etc., and 'Pilate!'), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - "The Road to Nowhere," NYR - Mad letters (A-sem. etc., and 'Pilate!'), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - "Eurothoughts", circa 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Review of "Koba the Dread: Laughter and the Twenty Million," TNR, draft, notes, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - "The Wrong War and the Wrong Time," NYT, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - "America's Restive Partners," NYT, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "America's Restive Partners," NYT, notes, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "America's Restive Partners," NYT, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "The West is Splitting and Bush's People Hardly Seem to Care," The Evening Standard, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Der Euro ist ein Nebensache," Der Standard, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "'Terror' als Mantra unserer Zeit," Tages-Anzeiger, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "We'll Always Have Paris," review of Paris 1919, NYT, draft, notes, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR,, drafts, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR,, drafts, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, notes, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, notes, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Its Own Worst Enemy," review of The Paradox of American Power, NYR, research, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - "After Victory," review of Six Days of War, TNR, notes, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - "After Victory," review of Six Days of War, TNR, drafts, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, draft, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, notes, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, notes, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - "Anti-Americans Abroad," review, NYR, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, draft, notes, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - "America and the World," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - "The Way We Live Now," review of The War Over Iraq, NYR, drafts, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - "The Way We Live Now," review of The War Over Iraq, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - "The Way We Live Now," review of The War Over Iraq, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - "The Way We Live Now," review of The War Over Iraq, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, drafts, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, drafts, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - "The Last Romantic," review of Interesting Times: A Twentieth-Century Life, NYR, research, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, similar piece for L.A. Times, reviews, responses, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, reviews, responses, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, "re: Israel" responses, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, "re: Israel" responses, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, "re: Israel" responses, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, "35 letters re: Tony Judt" (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, "35 letters re: Tony Judt" (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, "35 letters re: Tony Judt" (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Bi-National Israel (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Bi-National Israel (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Bi-National Israel (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Anti (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Anti (responses), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Anti (responses), 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Anti (responses), 2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Anti (responses), 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Nasty (responses), 2003 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "Israel: The Alternative," NYR, Nasty (responses), 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Gross-Israel Oder Binationaler Staat: Eine alternative Zukunft," Le Monde Diplomatique, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Two Visions," Newsweek International, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Dreams of Empire," review of 9 books on an American imperialism, NYR, drafts, research, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "Dreams of Empire," review of 9 books on an American imperialism, NYR, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - "Dreams of Empire," review of 9 books on an American imperialism, NYR, drafts, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Dreams of Empire," review of 9 books on an American imperialism, NYR, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "Dreams of Empire," review of 9 books on an American imperialism, NYR, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - "Dreams of Empire," review of 9 books on an American imperialism, NYR, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "The Cult of Contrition," The Independent, research, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - NYT Anti-Americanism, research, circa 2004 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "A Matter of Public Trust," Newsweek, draft, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Taking Another Look at Spain," Newsweek, drafts, notes correspondence, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Forward to Edward Said's From Oslo to Iraq, also appears as "Edward Said: The Rootless Cosmopolitan," in The Nation, draft, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Forward to Edward Said's From Oslo to Iraq, also appears as "Edward Said: The Rootless Cosmopolitan," in The Nation, draft, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Forward to Edward Said's From Oslo to Iraq, also appears as "Edward Said: The Rootless Cosmopolitan," in The Nation, draft, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "The Eastern Front, 2004," NYT, draft (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - "The Eastern Front, 2004," NYT (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - "George Bush et la confiance," Courier International, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - "Eine Art Sieg," Süddeutsche Zeitung, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - "The World We Have Lost," Newsweek International, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - "Alle bedauern, niemand ist verantwortlich," Tages-Anzeiger (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - "Quien lo siente ahora?" El Malpensante, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - "Europe Finds No Counterweight to U.S. Power," NYT, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - "A Sorry State: The Artlessness of the Apology," Washington Post, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - "Bush's 'apology' doesn't make nice," Newsday, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - "The Tony Machine," Newsweek, draft, notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - "Jak naprawdę funkcjonuje dzisiejszy świat," Europa Tygodnik Idei, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - "Goodbye To All That," Prospect, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - "Goodbye to All That?" The Nation, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - "Zaplata: Prawda o denazyfikacji," Europa Tyogdnik Idei, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Notes, research for NYT piece on French vote on EU constitution, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Notes, research for NYT piece on French vote on EU constitution, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, research, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, research, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, research, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, research, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, research, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, research, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - "The New World Order," review of books and reports on American militarism and Iraq war, NYR, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - "Europe vs. America," review of 3 books, NYR, drafts, research, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - "Europe vs. America," review of 3 books, NYR, research, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - "Europe vs. America," review of 3 books, NYR, research, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - "Europe vs. America," review of 3 books, NYR, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - "Europe vs. America," review of 3 books, NYR, notes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - "Neue Weltordnung," Lettre International, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - "From the House of the Dead: On Modern European Memory," NYR, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - "A Lobby, Not a Conspiracy," NYT, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - "A Story Still to be Told," review of The Cold War: A New History, NYR, notes, drafts, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - "A Story Still to be Told," review of The Cold War: A New History, NYR, notes, research, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - "Israel at 58," Haaretz, research, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - "Israel at 58," Haaretz, drafts, notes, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - "Israel at 58," Haaretz, research, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - "Israel at 58," Haaretz, research, notes, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - "Izrael kończy 58 lat," Europa Tygodnik Idei, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - "Goodbye to All That?" NYR piece on Leszek Kolakowski, drafts, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - "Goodbye to All That?" NYR piece on Leszek Kolakowski, research, notes, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - "Goodbye to All That?" NYR piece on Leszek Kolakowski, research, notes, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - "Goodbye to All That?" NYR piece on Leszek Kolakowski, research, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - "Goodbye to All That?" NYR piece on Leszek Kolakowski, research, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - "Bush's Useful Idiots," LRB liberal intellectuals FT, 803, etc. Sept. 2006 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - "Bush's Useful Idiots," LRB liberal intellectuals FT, 803, etc. Sept. 2006 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - "Pożyteczni idioci Busha," Europa Tygodnik Idei, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Review of American Vertigo by Bernard-Henri Lévy, The New Yorker, drafts, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Review of American Vertigo by Bernard-Henri Lévy, The New Yorker, notes, research, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, drafts, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, drafts, research, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, research, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, notes, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, notes, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, notes, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "Is the UN Doomed?" review of 3 books, NYR, research, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Polacy Zaskoczyli," Europa Tygodnik Idei, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "France Looks Ahead, and It Doesn't Look Good," NYT, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Tornen Els Falcons Liberals," L'Avenç, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Buldozer innowaecji," Europa-Tvgodnic Idei, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Review of The Narcissism of Minor Differences, manuscript, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - LRB letter to the editor in response to review of Fritz Stern book - notes, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Defender of the Faith," NYT review of Sacred Causes, notes, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "Defender of the Faith," NYT review of Sacred Causes, drafts, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - "The Wrecking Ball of Innovation," review of Supercapitalism, NYR, notes, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - "The Wrecking Ball of Innovation," review of Supercapitalism, NYR, notes, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - "The Wrecking Ball of Innovation," review of Supercapitalism, NYR, notes, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - "The Problem of Evil in Postwar Europe," Outlook, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - "La Vera Lezione di Auschwitz," Il Sole 24 Ore, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - "Z Domu Umarłych," Przeglad Polityczny: Powojnie, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - "Żegnaj, markizmie?" Tygodnik Powszechny, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - "Leszek Kolakowski (1927-2009)," NYR (Box 16, Folder 26)